Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Amazing Bulala
Episode 2
This is a cave
rift
Who is the mysterious man Wolffy and I met in the rift?
I wonder if we can go back through the rift.
Speaking of which, what about Wolffy?
Wolffy
where are you
This is
Wolffy’s hat
What is it?
Why does a rift appear in grassland?
I suspect it has something to do with the explosion last night
Big Humphrey
I, Planie, am here to help.
It would be great if you came
Only you can solve this matter
This time it all depends on you, Slowy.
let me see
this kind of thing
I haven’t seen it either
I need some tools to investigate
Mr. Slowy, I’ll go get the toolbox for you.
Mr. Slowy, toolbox
Have you met Weslie?
I’m going to find Weslie right away.
Weslie is missing
We can’t find him anywhere
Could he have gone to find Wolffy?
Not good
Wolffy is missing
Wolnie
did you see him
Wolffy didn’t come back all night
what happened
Look
Such exquisite Bulala
I don’t know if this Bulala can be eaten.
I have never seen such a big Bulala before
It hurts so much
Where is this?
Monster, don’t come here
hello
Don’t eat me
Who are you
You are Planie
Big Humphrey save me
Big Humphrey, Tyger
Why have you turned into fur dolls?
What happened to Goats’ Village?
What Goats’ Village
This is the Bulala City
Ragdolls Tyger and Big Humphrey
and
Bulala City?
In other corners of the universe
There may also be various wonderful worlds
Could it be that the rift leads to other worlds?
You don’t have to be afraid
I’m not a monster
I’m from somewhere else
want to find someone
I don’t know if you have seen him
It turns out he’s from other towns.
Who are you looking for?
he is a wolf
Probably something like this
It turns out that wolves look like this
Looks silly
A bit cruel
According to his characteristics
There is no doubt that he is a wolf
A wolf?
This scene seems a bit familiar.
I know
I saw him being taken away by people from the city
you can go there and have a look
You have to disguise yourself
Otherwise the soldiers here will take away a Bulala like you.
It seems that these Bulala are very important to them.
Give way
I’m in a hurry
They are actually collecting cotton clouds
May I ask why you collect these?
What are you talking about?
This is the Bulala we depend on for survival
Why don’t you hurry up and collect it?
I’d better go to the city quickly and find Wolffy.
Big Humphrey told me not to go the wrong way
The left side of the intersection leads to a cave.
There’s a scary monster living inside
You must not go
It’s really dangerous
I’d better leave quickly
How? Did you find them?
no
No
It’s like they disappeared from the whole world
Could it be
they ran in
They won’t get into the rifts
As soon as they discovered such a strange thing
they will definitely notify us before taking any action.
Yes, Wolffy will also report it first.
But this time there is no news at all
Mommy, look
Is this Daddy’s invention?
Wolffy’s Exploding Paper Plane
Then let’s go in and save people quickly.
Wait, everything inside is unknown.
If you go in hastily, you won’t be able to do anything.
But Wolffy and Weslie are inside
We’re not sure if they’re in there either
I don’t know where this rift leads to
or whether there’s any danger.
what is that
What’s this
There’s something here too
Why do these two materials blend together?
kids
help me collect things
to the lab for research
Okay
Mr. Slowy
Planie
What are you still doing?
You also come to help
Set off
It’s really far away
It’s almost there. It’s almost there.
What an amazing skill
Help, who can help me?
Help, I’m so scared
Then let go
But I want to pick Bulala
Then climb up
But I’m afraid
Don’t be afraid I’m coming
I can’t stand it anymore
Come
hold me
What’s going on
this person
looks similar to me
thank you for saving me
you
Look similar to me
You don’t look like a Bulala
I’m from a place called Green Green Grassland
Because something unexpected happened
I’m here
By the way, have you ever seen this person?
I’ve seen
where have you seen him
I saw him being picked up and brought home by a grandfather in the city
Then can you take me to him now?
But I am picking Bulala now.
The time to pay tribute is very close
It will be bad if I don’t pay.
Why do you want to pay Bulala?
What is this rule?
Actually, I didn’t have to pay it originally.
But because not long ago
A monster ran out of nowhere
The monster has sharp claws and destroys everywhere
Fortunately, Master Quan discovered that the monster liked Bulala
Let everyone offer Bulala to appease the monster
Sure enough, the monster didn’t trouble us anymore after receiving Bulala.
since then
All the Bulala we collect will be handed over to the soldiers
Give it to the monster
only
the Monster needs
more and more Bulala
Bulala
is getting harder and harder to pick.
Extra Large Bulala
The quality of this Bulala is really good
Wait, he’s not
I’m not
Can still talk
Since I was little, I have imagined that Bulala would talk to me
let me go
I’m not Bulala
This Bulala can still move
It can’t run away now
That, he is not
Please wait for that
What? Is there something else?
He he is not my Bulala
That’s just right
This is the Bulala we picked
It’s such good material
How could a coward like you collect it?
No, this is mine
No matter if it’s yours or not
It’s ours now
but but
waste our time
What should I do now
He’s going to be sacrificed to the monster
This rare Bulala is really good
When we get back, we’ll shave off his Bulala.
Master Quan must be very happy to see it
reject
Great, run quickly
He runs fast
Rare Bulala
It’s Wolffy’s sticker
The situation is different now
You can’t catch me, right?
Thanks to Wolffy
You can’t even catch a single Bulala. Really useless.
Your batch of Bulala
is under our control now.
To be continued